It's been a while, but
ちょっと時間が経っちゃったけど、
It's been a while.
久しぶりでございます
yes.
はい
It's Aiko Haruzu.
あいこはるずだね
Is it tighter or more toned?
つんぎゃっていうか、さらに引き締まった?
Maybe.
もしかして
I agree.
そうですね
hey.
ね
As expected, who is it?
さすがに誰だね
I'm exercising at this time of year.
運動してるんで、この時期は
hey.
ね
What do you think?
どうですか?
There is a gap between the edges,
この間のエッジから間空いてるけど、
Who did you meet during that time?
その間に誰かとしたの?
No, I haven't.
いや、してないです
Ah, I'm a little happy, aren't I?
あ、ちょっと嬉しいじゃないですか
For us.
我々にとっては
So, is that a bit?
で、ちょっとあれですか?
Are you feeling a little horny?
ちょっとムラムラしてる感じですか?
yes.
はい
After all, athletes are like that.
やっぱね、アスリートはそうだよね
I'm pretty horny.
大体ムラムラしてるよね
Is that so?
そうですかね
With that in mind, today I'm a bit of an athlete.
そう思って、今日はちょっとね、アスリートっていうか、
I called a judoka.
柔道家を呼んじゃった
picture?
え?
Just because I like it.
ちょっとね、好みだっつって
She loves sports, sports, and sports girls.
スポーツ、スポーツ、スポーツ系の女子大好きだっつって
It's a style.
スタイルですね
You like it, right?
好きでしょう?
I love it.
大好きです
Well, what kind of events are you doing?
えっと、種目は何やってるんですか?
But it's a short distance.
でも短距離です
ERROR
僕短距離さん選手大好きなんですね
速そうな足してるでしょ
No, no, no.
いや いやいや
Your feet are really beautiful.
ほんと足綺麗っすね
I'll step on this earth with my feet.
この足であれを、この大地を踏みしめるんだよ
ERROR
大地を踏みしめる
Truck, look, these legs.
トラックを、ほら、この足を
This is embarrassing.
恥ずかしいな、これ
This foot.
この足
ERROR
まあ、こうなるよね
Well, that's how it goes.
まあ、こうなっちゃうわけ
If I were to be reborn, it would be shoes.
生まれ変わるならシューズだね
Okay, this is a little bit.
いいっすね、これちょっと
I want to be an insole.
中敷きになりたい
ERROR
入り足すぎて、結構ちょっと立ちなんですかね
People who exercise stand up quickly.
運動やってる人はね、すぐ立っちゃう
But I guess that's true.
それはでも、そうなんですかね
After all, it's a matter of order.
や っぱり順度だから
ERROR
性力なんちょっと、一緒にちょっと強いらしくて
Are you good at matching?
似合わせは得意なんですか?
You're good at matching.
似合わせは得意っすね
He's good at holding things down.
押さえ込めが得意っすね
結
Structure: Two people, two people.
構 2人、2人だから
It's true, it's true.
当たりますね、当たりますね
A little bit for me too.
私にもちょっと
Is this what Jane is saying?
これ、ジェインのそうですか?
You can guess.
当てれます
Oh my god, I'm awake right now because they're kissing.
やばい、今2人のキスで俺起きてる
Maybe I have a bit of a cuckold tendency.
なんか俺、ちょっと寝取られの性癖があるのかもしれない
I felt like I was being cuckolded right now.
今、なんか寝取られてる気がしたの
I like it.
好きです
I was a little confused about my hands.
ちょっと迷ったね、手が
It's okay, it's okay.
いいんだよ、いいんだよ
My hands are lost now.
今、手が迷った
I'm not embarrassed at all, at all.
全然恥ずかしくないですよ、全然
It's really good.
めちゃくちゃいいですよ
Erotic and cute.
エロかわいい
Isn't your tingling a bit obvious?
ちょっと、チクビもっきりしてるんじゃない?
difficult.
難しい
What will you do?
どうされますか?
What will happen?
どうされるの?
Please.
お願いしまーす
I also like being touched in my dreams.
夢で触られるのも好きだ
death.
し
I also like the smell of athletes, right?
ア スリートの匂いも好きだよね、
Really.
本当にね
I'm really amazing.
本当に僕すごい
I also like the smell of cute babies.
可愛い子の匂いも好きなんですよ
The name athlete is also good.
アスリートって名も良し
If you do that, there will be a smell of sweat.
そういうことしてくれたら、汗の匂いがあるんだよね
ERROR
えっ、そんなに?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
When I changed that, tsk.
それを変えた時、チンッ
I can see your six pack.
シックスパック見えてるからね
amazing.
すごい
Do you understand?
わかる?
Right?
そうでしょ?
That's what happens, isn't it?
そうなっちゃいますよね
ERROR
硬くていい
It's true, on my futon.
俺の布団に、 本当だね
I never get tired of looking at this style.
見てて飽きないけどね、このスタイルが
It's insanely good for a model, isn't it?
め ちゃくちゃ、 モデル割りに上手いですよね
It's good to train regularly.
普段鍛えてると良いんだ
ERROR
良い食い込みですね
That's true, isn't it?
それがちゃんとあるよね
It's a plan plan.
プランプランですけど
It's been trained and this butt is amazing.
鍛えられてて、このお尻は最高ですよ
It's rising sharply.
キュッと上がってるからね
It's like snow.
雪みたいのです
You want to fuck me in, right?
ぶち込みたいでしょ?
You want to get fucked in this outfit, right?
この格好でぶち込みたいでしょ?
I want to do it.
やりたい
I really want to do it, but just a little bit.
すごいやりたいけど、ちょっと
Now, just hit your hips a little with the air,
今、エアーでちょっと、 腰だけ打ち込んで、
Just leave it in the air.
エアーでそのまま
It's come, it's come.
来た来た
Isn't it like this?
こんな感じでしょ?
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
This is the best.
これ最高
A little from the right, a little from the right.
右からちょっと、右からちょっと
The fit here is amazing.
ここフィット感がすごい
It's just there to hit the dick.
チンコを当てるためだけにある
My prediction is that it's closing.
僕の予想のところ、締めてるんですよ
It's a long time.
時間が長い
30 minutes.
30分
What should I do?
どうしようか
Can you tighten it?
締めてくれる?
Let's hug you forever.
ずっと抱きまくれにしよう
Want to see it?
見たい?
I want to see it.
見たい
Don't you usually process it?
普段処理しないの?
this.
これ
I don't do it much.
あんまりしない
Not much?
あんまりしない?
Why is that?
それはなんで?
I wish I was practicing.
練 習とかしてたらね
I don't even have a boyfriend.
彼氏とかもいないし
Since I am exercising, my hormones are released a lot.
運動してるから、ホルモンめちゃめちゃ出ちゃってる
That's why it was so solid.
だからこれだけしっかりした
I also want to share my hormones.
俺もホルモンを分けてほしいな
Not very much.
あ ん まり しない
Can I take one home?
一本持って帰っていいですか?
Can I put it in my wallet?
お財布に入れてもいいですか?
I'm going in.
入るんで
Wha Shizukami?
わ しづかみ?
It's just me.
わしづかみじゃん
It's a really nasty hormone.
めちゃめちゃ嫌らしいホルモンじゃん
Isn't it a bit erotic?
ちょっとエロいじゃない?
I don't know.
分からない
This is a little erotic.
ちょっとエロいよ、これ
This is an athlete's pussy.
アスリートマンコだよ、これ
It's a meaty hair monster, this is a little.
肉髪モンコですね、これちょっと
Always think of it as training, and keep it heavy.
いつもトレーニングだと思って、 重量キープで
Isn't this already wet?
すでに、これ 濡れてません?
If you look closely now, you'll see that you're holding your breath.
ちょっと今、よーく見てたら 息をひいてるね、
this.
これ
It gets wet really easily, I guess.
すごい濡れやすい、もしかして
It might get wet easily.
濡れやすいかもね
I guess it's because I have more energy.
精力強めなのかな、ちょっと
Even if I go there for the second time, it's still a masterpiece.
2回目に行っても、 名機だよね、
absolute.
絶対
In fact, it's a masterpiece.
実 際、名機なんだけど
The way it gets wet, the suction is a bit thick.
この濡れ方の この吸い付きはちょっと この肉厚なね
I think this is a nice pussy.
これがちょっといい マンコだと思うんですけど
What do you think?
どうでしょうか?
There is a bloodline, a bloodline.
血筋がちゃんとあるもん、血筋が
Well, that's right.
や っぱね、そうなんですよ
Muscles, after all.
筋肉がね、やっぱね
This is the second pussy.
2体目のマンコだ、これ
This is the second one.
これが2体目
Do you do any training?
鍛えるトレーニングとかしてるの?
I haven't.
してない
Do you have a map tray or something?
地図トレーとかしてる?
I hear something, but...
なんか聞くけど、なんか
The girls in Minato Ward often do this.
港区女子がよくやってるってやつ
map training
地図トレ
Ning.
ーニ ング
What are you doing?
何してる?
No matter what I do.
何とやっても
a,
あ、
If we talk about map training, that's what it means.
地 図トレーニングの話を振ったら そういうことなのね
It's perfect for training, as training equipment.
なんか トレーニングにさ、 トレーニング器具にちょうどいいん
That's why I brought this today.
じゃない かと思って 今日これ持ってきたんだ
Did you bring it?
持ってきたんですか?
It can be used as a training tool.
トレーニング器具として使える
This is especially a massager, isn't it?
これ特にマッサージ器でしょ、これ
Tired muscles.
疲れた筋肉とか
firmly.
固く
Also, the nipples.
あと、乳首も
nipple
乳首
It squeaks when you hit it.
に 当てるとキュッてする
Clift and Howardoch?
クリフトとハワドッチですか?
Let's go.
行ってみよう
I'm getting wet again.
また濡れてきた
Yeah, I'm kind of tingling.
そう、なんかヒクヒクしてる
Very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very.
ごくごくめちゃくちゃごく
Aren't you going to ejaculate on your fingers?
指で射精しちゃうんじゃない?
I'm going to ejaculate a little.
ちょっと射精しちゃう
Yeah.
うん
Yes, I'm going.
はい、いっちゃう
Aren't your abs amazing?
腹筋すごくない?
This is how it evolves.
このように振った進化する
That's some nice abs.
いい腹筋だよ、これ
Maybe he won't do it for a while.
ちょっとしてくれないかもしれない
It's kind of shining really bright, isn't it?
なんかすごい光ってるけどないですか?
Yeah, a little bit.
うん、ちょっと
A vibe that can be used during times of grief.
悲傷自体の時に使えるバイブ
Is it for disaster use?
災害用ってこと?
Even for disasters.
災害用でも
I see.
なるほどね
This is perfect for disaster use.
災害用でも大丈夫だな、これ
災害用?
What is a disaster vibe?
災害用のバイブって何?
Look, it's glowing, right?
ほら、光るでしょ?
It's shining, it's shining.
光ってる、光ってる
You can tell where your pussy is even at night.
夜でもおまんこの位置分かるってやつ
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
I can't see the hole.
穴が分からない
What should I do?
どうしようって
Sometimes I don't know where the hole is.
穴が分からないことある
This is the one that was selling TV shopping.
これテレビショッピング売ってたやつだ
Is this sold on TV shopping?
テレビショッピングでこれ売ってんの?
oh yeah.
そうそう
That's amazing.
すごいね
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
Look.
ほら
So I'm curious about where TV shopping is.
じゃあどこのテレビショッピングか気になるから、
Tell me later.
後で教えて
The exit is shining.
出口が光ってる
It's weird, the way you're so into it.
やらしいね、なんかこのめり込み方がね
It's good to remove it.
抜くといいね
It's like you're completely following me.
すっかりついてくるってなっちゃうんだね
Does it feel good to be pounded?
なんかドボドボされて気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
My abs are twitching like hell.
めちゃめちゃ腹筋ピクピクしてる
Ah, my abs are twitching.
あ、腹筋ピクピク
I'm doing it.
して る
My abdominal muscles moved tremendously.
すごい腹筋動いちゃった
Double chat stops after all.
ちょっとダブルチャットやっぱり止まっちゃう
Is it closed?
閉じてる?
Amazing abs.
すごい腹筋
You see, the fluttering inside of my pussy,
マンコのほら、この中のひらひらがさ、
Like this.
こうやって
It feels like Cuba, but this.
キューバーみたいな感じだけどこれ
Let's do it.
や るよ
There's a lot to see.
見ててすっげー多いよね
It feels good.
気持ちいいそう
It's better not to have a boyfriend.
彼氏作んない方がいいよ
If you get a boyfriend, he won't be able to do these things for you.
彼氏作るとね、こういうことしてもらえなくなっちゃう
I object as a dumpling.
団子として反対します
As a dumpling.
団子としてね
From someone you like.
好きな方から
From your favorite chin chin.
お好きなチンチンから
I like it too.
私も好き
Would you like to go out with me?
俺と付き合おうか
If we started dating there, I wouldn't be able to have sex.
そこで付き合っちゃうと俺、セックスできなくなるじゃん
I'll call you.
呼んであげるから
Yes, you can be criticized for not talking like that.
そう、そんな話ししないで舐められる
Ah, that was better.
あ、そっちの方がよかったんだ
That's a hell of a pussy.
めちゃくちゃ口マンコだね
Wait a minute, this pella is really good.
ちょっと待って、このペラめちゃくちゃ上手いぞ
Compare yourself to someone you like.
好きな人に比べてください
Compare it to someone who likes dick.
おチンチンが好きな人に比べてください
It's the one that makes you speechless, it's seriously disgusting.
無言になるやつでしょ、マジで気持ち悪くしてる
Tuck your hips.
腰ひっくりして
Yes, answer.
はい、答え
You like butts, right?
お尻好きだよね
really like.
大好き
Please show me your butt.
お尻見せてください
Just stay like this, be fluent.
このままさ、ペラペラして
Just the butt.
お尻だけ
Isn't that ass the best?
そのお尻最高じゃない?
Is it bad to give a blow job?
フェラシリってよくない?
Fellatio, women's butts.
フェラシリ、女子のお尻
Her butt sways naturally.
自然に揺れるお尻ね
Why don't you turn your butt a little towards me?
ちょっとだけお尻こっち向けない?
Are you shaking?
揺れちゃってるの?
In the butt.
お尻に
It's not shaking, it's not shaking.
揺 れてない、揺れてない
It's already tight in the butt.
もうお尻にこっちにしっかりしてる
I might be a little lazy after all.
やっぱりちょっとペラしてるかも
Can I put this in as is?
これ、このまま入れていい?
put in?
入れる?
Can I come in?
入 れて いい?
this.
これ
I want to put it in.
入れたいよ
入れたい
Can I put in Damchinchin?
ダムチンチン入れていい?
this.
これ
Is it okay?
いいの?
Won't you say no later?
後でダメとか言わない?
this.
これ
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
Because I want to put it in.
入れちゃいたいから
The butt that can be seen from this side is also super dangerous.
こっち側から見えるお尻も超ヤバい
It's really good.
めちゃめちゃ良い
The butt seen from above is also really good.
上から見るお尻もめちゃくちゃ良い
A little too much of a butt.
お尻割りすぎちょっと
Is it in?
入ってる?
Do you understand?
分かる?
this.
これ
I understand.
分かる
The hair is on top of that base.
そのベースの上が髪だって
I have a little hair below my waist.
腰の下がちょっと髪なんだけど
Ah, just everything.
あー、ちょっと全部
It's pretty clean though.
しょっぷきん綺麗なんだけど
This background is amazing.
背景がすごいよ、これ
Wow, what a great plot.
うわー、すごい筋が
You're moving a lot of muscles.
すんごい筋肉が動いてるね
You can see it moving even if you look at it from here.
こっちから見てても動いてるの分かるよ
It's a mess.
くちゃくちゃいってるね
Screw it up, get it together.
くちゃくちゃ、すびつけよ
Because I want to have a little gun,
ちょっとガン付きしたいから、
this.
これ
It's thin and light, so go for this one.
細 くて軽いから、この方に来てね
It feels really good.
やっぱめっちゃ気持ちいい
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
ヤバいよ、危ねー
Her face is too cute.
顔可愛すぎて
too
も
Because I'm going to hold you tight.
ち もち握っちゃうから
My waist is squeezed.
腰を絞られる
Hit your hips yourself.
自分で腰を打ち付けて
This is so erotic.
これ、エロいよね
This butt is so beautiful.
このお尻、めちゃくちゃ綺麗だから
Can I be attacked from behind?
後ろからガン付きしていい?
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
Can I step on it?
足掛けてもいい?
Chase me.
追いかけて
It's really dark.
すごい濃いね
It felt pretty good, right?
相当気持ちよかったでしょ?
It felt amazing.
すごい気持ちよかった
Can I put it in my stomach?
お腹に出していい?
This feeling.
この気に
I wanted to go home.
帰りたくてきちゃった
I just stuck my butt out a little bit.
さっきちょっとお尻出したんだけどさ
One more time, okay?
もう一回、いいよね
This made me feel full.
お腹いっぱい出されたね、これ
Oh no, kiss.
やばい、キス
This isn't quiet.
これ、静くないで
Let's have sex again.
また、セックスしよう
I want to do it again.
またしたいって
I found out.
バレた
I understand.
わかるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You want to eat it all, right?
ズボズボさえたいでしょ
Isn't it a little wet?
ちょっと濡れてるんじゃない?
I'm getting wet.
濡れちゃう
sleep?
寝る?
I'm starting to sleep really hard and I'm about to get fucked.
すっごい寝だしにこれからぶち込まれるんだよ
I told you it felt good.
気持ちいいって言っちゃったね
If it's a bed, let it out comfortably.
寝床だったら気持ちよく出しよう
Yukku
ゆっく
ri, slowly.
り、 ゆっくり